Contact

7068298025 (Work) emily.daitch@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/emilydaitch (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

Embedded Software
Continuous Improvement

Emily Daitch

EDP at John Deere

Atlanta

Summary

Forget about being an expert or a professional, and wear your amateurism (your heart, your love) on your sleeve. Share what you love, and the people who love the same things will find you."

- Austin Kleon, Show Your Work

Hello, my name is Emily! Ask me about my international beginners web development study group (I moderate, and am not a web development professional).

Feel free to reach out to me.

Experience

John Deere

2 years 3 months

EDP

July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Des Moines, Iowa Area

- Electronics Engineering Group Sprayers Des Moines Works Factory, Ankeny, IA
- Refactoring C++ software to support implementing AutoSAR on John Deere Sprayers
- Developing MBSD components in MATLAB Simulink for use in the AutoSAR ecosystem
- Section Control Intelligent Solutions Group (ISG) Urbandale, IA
- Lead developer of Manual Overlap Control App to provide more accurate yield data
- Contributed production software from Presentation layer down to Communication layer,
 manipulating objects sent to other ECUs
- Automation Delivery Organization ISG Urbandale, IA

- Learned Docker to containerize and modernize a legacy test environment, improving security
- Integrated the virtualized environment with Jenkins during shift to AWS cloud
- Refactored 20+ Jenkinsfiles

Rainbow Employee Resource Group Member June 2018 - June 2020 (2 years 1 month)

- Organized resume review session with University of NC LGBT students
- Presented Educational LGBT material to a D&I curated diversity initiative "Emily, thank you for your willingness to share your story so openly during the 3 Rainbow/Men as Diversity Partners engagements. You are truly amazing and I am inspired by your bravery. You have made a lasting impact on many people at John Deere. You are a gem and I am lucky to call you my friend."

John Deere Product Development Intern June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months) Cary, NC

- Accelerated log analysis by automating detection of faulty signals
- Worked with Vector CANalyzer to solve engine-controller defects
- Tool design done in C-based CAPL (CAN Application Programming Language)

Georgia Institute of Technology Low Frequency Radio Lab Undergraduate Research Assistant August 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Greater Atlanta Area

- Prototyped a portable radio receiver to combat phase instability in the field
- Using BeagleBone Black Programmable Real-Time Units and Digilent FGPA
- Best Research Presentation Award 2016 and 2017

John Deere Software Developement Intern May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months) Des Moines, Iowa Area

- Personally developed 3D-visualization playback tool for troubleshooting CV applications
- Gained experience with boost, Qt, and OpenCV
- Built HIL pipe to transmit images from a camera over the network to a Guidance Algorithm

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology
BS Computer Engineering · (2013 - 2017)